Unlock the illusion.
Now You See Me: Now You Don't is a thriller, crime,
mystery film directed by Ruben Fleischer.
The original Four Horsemen reunite with a new generation of illusionists to take on powerful diamond heiress
Veronika Vanderberg, who leads a criminal empire built on money laundering and trafficking.
The new and old magicians must overcome their differences to
work together on their most ambitious heist yet.
J. Daniel Atlas, played by Jesse Eisenberg.
Bosco, played by Dominic Sessa.
June, played by Ariana Greenblatt.
Charlie, played by Justice Smith.
Veronika Vanderberg, played by Rosamund Pike.
Merritt McKinney, played by Woody Harrelson.
Now You See Me: Now You Don't is a 2025 American heist film directed by Ruben Fleischer from a screenplay by Michael Lesslie, the
writing duo of Paul Wernick and Rhett Reese, and Seth Grahame-Smith, based on a story by Eric Warren Singer and Lesslie.
The film is the sequel to  Now You See Me 2 (2016) and the third
installment in the  Now You See Me film series.
The cast includes Jesse Eisenberg, Woody Harrelson, Dave Franco, Isla Fisher, Lizzy Caplan, and Morgan Freeman returning from
previous films, joined by new cast members Justice Smith, Dominic Sessa, Ariana Greenblatt, and Rosamund Pike.
Now You See Me: Now You Don't premiered at the Harbour Club in Amsterdam, Netherlands, on November
11, 2025, and was released in the United States on November 14, 2025, by Lionsgate.
The film grossed $240 million worldwide and received mixed reviews from critics.
A sequel is in development.
The film explores themes of diamond, antwerp, sequel, heist, diamond heist.
The tone is mind_bending and intense.